this tutorial is about hubs and pivots
本教程是关于枢轴和枢轴的
这是加入两张卡的方式
this tutorial is about hubs and pivots
it's ways of joining two pieces of card
在一起，所以他们很平坦，他们可以
在这种情况下，你有这个
it's ways of joining two pieces of card
together so they're flat and they can
转盘上有一个窗户
轮和图像在页面上
together so they're flat and they can
turn in this case you've got this
在它后面，也可以使用它
周围的方式，以便您在
turn in this case you've got this
turning wheel it's got a window in the
转动滚轮页面时图像
改变这就是你做到的方式
turning wheel it's got a window in the
wheel and the images are on the page
基本上有一个带孔的轮子
它，然后您有了这个集线器，集线器是
wheel and the images are on the page
behind it or you can use it the other
只是一个带有两个小圆环
折叠起来的标签贴在页面上
behind it or you can use it the other
way around so you have a window in the
他们通过方向盘折叠起来
再往下放，所以在这个例子中
way around so you have a window in the
page as you turn the wheel the image
这就是集线器的外观
是两个小皮瓣，然后这个
page as you turn the wheel the image
changes this is the way you make it
蓝色的一块被卡住了
稳定只是将其压低
changes this is the way you make it
basically there's a wheel with a hole in
移动有拍打的趋势
抬起一点，这样可以很好
basically there's a wheel with a hole in
it and then you have this hub the hub is
加强它，所以我就把它放在
在一起，以便您可以轻松了解
it and then you have this hub the hub is
just a circular piece with two little
工作，然后我告诉你一些
例如，当您将胶水涂在身上时
just a circular piece with two little
tabs that fold up it sticks to the page
只是把它放在主体上
集线器和所有这些拉带
tabs that fold up it sticks to the page
they come up through the wheel and fold
不需要胶水的类型机制
渗出液或确实使工程胶化
they come up through the wheel and fold
down flat again and so in this example
阻止他们移动我已经
标记前进的方向，以便车轮将
down flat again and so in this example
this is what the hub looks like these
符合基本页面的要求
所以它很容易转，所以有
this is what the hub looks like these
are the two little flaps and then this
皮瓣向你割去的地方
不想太紧或太松散
are the two little flaps and then this
blue piece has been stuck on to hold it
车轮只是摇晃，所以你
需要它相当精确以适合
blue piece has been stuck on to hold it
steady just to hold it all down as it
轮，在这里你可以看到所以也许
再次，如果我在上面加上一些标记，您会
steady just to hold it all down as it
moves there's a tendency for the flaps
能够看到它如何更轻松地移动
所以显然有旋转
moves there's a tendency for the flaps
to lift up a bit so it can be quite good
很容易，所以我只看一些
书中有妮娜（Nina）的变色龙（Leon）
to lift up a bit so it can be quite good
to reinforce it so I'll just put this on
可以牛吗，这是这里有一个枢纽
在页面后面启用
to reinforce it so I'll just put this on
together so you can see easily how it
变色龙的颜色随您而改变
绕着它继续前进
together so you can see easily how it
works and then I'll show you some
然后是David Pellom的这本书
很棒的书，这是一本
works and then I'll show you some
examples so when you put the glue on you
您转动方向盘中的文本
窗口不断前进，其中之一
examples so when you put the glue on you
just put it onto the main body of the
这些在每页上，所以如果我们看这个
一个文本在底部
just put it onto the main body of the
hub and again with all these pull strip
翻到这里的页面，我们可以
看到文字不断前进，所以这
hub and again with all these pull strip
type mechanisms you don't want the glue
yam pions Kowski的自动书机
这是一个很好的例子
type mechanisms you don't want the glue
oozing or it really gums up the works
转动时方向盘位于页面后面
你得到这些光学元件，这很漂亮
oozing or it really gums up the works
and stops them moving I've already
好，然后在另一边
当你转动它时，你有相同的轮子
and stops them moving I've already
marked where this goes so the wheel will
地球在窗户上旋转
实际的机制有很多
marked where this goes so the wheel will
fit with this bite out of the base page
不同的用途，所以我只告诉你
其中有些是真的
fit with this bite out of the base page
so it makes it easy to turn so there is
拉动有趣的有用机制
条带使图像在页面上
where the flaps are cut back to you
这就是机制的旋转方式
作品
where the flaps are cut back to you
don't want it too tight or too loose or
这是我们做的基本拉条
在教程25中，它具有此附加功能
don't want it too tight or too loose or
the wheel just wobbles around so you
轮毂上的拍子只是正常的帮助
就像我们在这里所做的，但在这种情况下
the wheel just wobbles around so you
need it fairly precise to fit within the
没有附在手臂上的页面
浏览页面并获得图像
need it fairly precise to fit within the
wheel and here you can see so maybe
粘在他们的另一个主体上
集线器的手臂再次卡在它上面
wheel and here you can see so maybe
again if I put some marks on this you'll
使这个两倍的厚度，因为它
确实承受了一些压力
again if I put some marks on this you'll
be able to see how it moves more easily
盖上皮瓣上的孔
移动量受此控制
be able to see how it moves more easily
so there is obviously just spins around
控制方向的袖子
控制方向的缝隙
so there is obviously just spins around
quite easily and so I just look at some
这两个控制方向
拉带他们也控制数量
quite easily and so I just look at some
books there's Leon the chameleon by Nina
运动，这是另一个例子
只是旋转的另一幅图像
books there's Leon the chameleon by Nina
can yak this is it there's a hub here
该页面是您可以看到的相同内容
有拉臂使手臂向前移动
can yak this is it there's a hub here
behind the page which is enabling the
集线器在这种情况下
用手臂制成的全部是一件
behind the page which is enabling the
color of the chameleon to change as you
这些要记住的另一件事
获得所需的最大运动
color of the chameleon to change as you
pull it around it just keeps moving on
拉带尽可能靠近轮毂
可能离它越远
pull it around it just keeps moving on
and then this book trail by David Pellom
集线器，您将获得的运动更少，因此请保持
尽可能地靠近它
and then this book trail by David Pellom
fantastic book this one so here it is as
我认为这只是其中之一
是的，这只是告诉你
fantastic book this one so here it is as
you turn the wheel the text in the
你如何才能真正让你振作起来
知道这是控制的州长
you turn the wheel the text in the
window keeps moving on there's one of
运动量只是一块
被卡在拉带上以停止
window keeps moving on there's one of
these on each page so if we look at this
它进一步向前移动
停止拉带的这一端拉
these on each page so if we look at this
one the text is down at the bottom of
从袖子里出来没有图像
随动
one the text is down at the bottom of
the page down here as we turn it you can
轮毂也可以用于连接
运动，这是一种机制
the page down here as we turn it you can
see the text keeps moving on so this
和我们刚才看的一样
那里有武装的枢纽
see the text keeps moving on so this
book robot by yam pions Kowski it's got
通过页面，它有一条手臂
通过它的襟翼附着在它上面
book robot by yam pions Kowski it's got
a nice example here where you've got the
在拉带上，当您拉动它时
与我们所看到的完全一样
a nice example here where you've got the
the wheel is behind the page as you turn
刚才在另一边
连锁店，这就是背后的枢纽
the wheel is behind the page as you turn
it you get these optics so that's pretty
这是被什么感动的
泳池地带，这里是一个
it you get these optics so that's pretty
good and then on the other side you've
附加到页面，然后这两个
将三张卡片链接为
good and then on the other side you've
got the same wheel as you turn it you
你把它拉整
明确表示您只能使用三个
got the same wheel as you turn it you
have the earth spinning in the window
你只有两只手，那是
三角剖分只是僵化，不会
the actual mechanism has a lot of
如果您有三个以上，则移动
这是一条链条，所以一端或另一端，但
the actual mechanism has a lot of
different uses so I'll just show you
另一头只是认为它没有做
他们会采取的任何行动
different uses so I'll just show you
some of those this is a really
周围，​​这很清楚是什么
这样做，有两个很好的例子
some of those this is a really
interesting useful mechanism as you pull
在NP的机器人中，科夫斯基有一个
明确表达的一个很好的例子
interesting useful mechanism as you pull
the strip it makes the image on the page
图像，这是妈妈机器人倾销
洗衣机中的婴儿机器人
the strip it makes the image on the page
rotate here's the way the mechanism
你把条带拉下来，宝贝
所以这又是三个部分
rotate here's the way the mechanism
works
附在拉条上的是
附加到页面上，另外两个
works
this is a basic pull strip that we did
依附在婴儿身上，如果我们看
从后面看到它，那里有
this is a basic pull strip that we did
in tutorial 25 it has this additional
拥有三个部分的两个枢纽
在一起，还有另一个例子
in tutorial 25 it has this additional
flap on it the hub is a normal help just
颜色使大学祈祷的人感到惊讶
大卫·佩洛姆（David Pellom）这是这条龙
flap on it the hub is a normal help just
like we made here but in this case it's
你拉地带龙是
清楚地说明了它在一个
like we made here but in this case it's
not attached to the page the arms go
不同的方式，但你可以看到拉
地带将附在中间
not attached to the page the arms go
through the page and have the image
在这里，然后这两个枢纽
将它们附加到页面上
through the page and have the image
stuck onto them the other main body of
事情可以随你而动
把它
stuck onto them the other main body of
the hub has this arm stuck on it again
我想告诉你另一个是
相当令人惊讶的动作
the hub has this arm stuck on it again
make this double thickness because it
当您拉开条带时，图像会突然出现
并延伸到整个页面，因此
make this double thickness because it
does take some stress that goes through
这种方式再次起作用的方式是
我们看过的基本拉条
does take some stress that goes through
the hole in the flap as you put it the
教程25这是襟翼
集线器集线器连接到页面，并且
the hole in the flap as you put it the
amount of movement is governed by this
然后这两个手臂上来去去
通过这片紫色的孔
amount of movement is governed by this
sleeve that controls the direction and
紫色的那块你要做
指南针，所以有三个圆圈
sleeve that controls the direction and
this slit that controls the direction so
这里然后一个这里一个
整个事物出现的缝隙
this slit that controls the direction so
those two control the direction of the
通过它瞄准的中心
所有这些圈子，所以它只是移动
those two control the direction of the
pull strip they also control the amount
通过它很顺利，所以这一点
需要很大的压力
pull strip they also control the amount
of movement and here's another example
范围很广，否则会弯曲
这个手臂也需要加倍
of movement and here's another example
it's just a different image rotating on
厚度或再次趋于弯曲
因为它确实需要很多
it's just a different image rotating on
the page it's the same thing you can see
再次强调一个非常令人愉悦的机制
而且您随时可以在
the page it's the same thing you can see
there's the pull strip moving the arm on
到这里结束，这样您就可以进行图像扫描了
在页面上，最后是另一个
there's the pull strip moving the arm on
the hub in this case the hub has been
非常奇怪的小变化是一样的
带盖的拉条的类型和
the hub in this case the hub has been
made with its arm it's all one piece the
控制方向的袖子，但
在这种情况下，它有两个小臂
made with its arm it's all one piece the
other thing to remember with these to
向下折叠的标签会推动
孔，以便该臂的末端是
other thing to remember with these to
get the maximum movement you need the
固定在那个方形的皮瓣上，然后整个
事情刚好通过这个洞
get the maximum movement you need the
pull strip to be as close to the hub as
拉动页面时，它会给您一个
您从正面看到的不同动作
pull strip to be as close to the hub as
possible the further away it is from the
在前面，你可以看到它给
与众不同的行动
possible the further away it is from the
hub the less movement you'll get so keep
看其他的枢纽和枢轴
在这两本书中有更详细的
hub the less movement you'll get so keep
it as close as you can when you're
矿
最新的弹出式设计和论文
it as close as you can when you're
making one of these this I think is just
机械师，但主题被看
本书弹出窗口中有更多详细信息
making one of these this I think is just
yeah this is just that just shows you
纸机制手册
不幸的是现在绝版了，但是你
yeah this is just that just shows you
how you can really just budge it up you
仍然可以获得二手副本
您
how you can really just budge it up you
know this is the governor that controls